[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What can we do about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's very dangerous to try to preventively detain people based on predictions of what they're liking to do in the future.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Because as there are more of them, the need to do something becomes more and more urgent, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "RBR", "CC", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I think that's exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Dan Baum, how do you make it harder for crazy people to legally buy weapons that they can go and do crazy things with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "A ROAD TRIP\": The first thing you do is you do no harm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan Baum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "What do you do about that culture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, of course it doesn't mean what you just said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Can I respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, I mean -- let me just -- before we go to Alan, what I would say is, it's very good to have the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "But this particular one of crazy people doing crazy things, what can you do to try and red flag these people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, homicide, murder, is a byproduct of many different qualities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What do we do about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Unless it is to do harm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Mass shooting is an end point in an individual who may have mental illness and who may not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Final question, though, I mean, from all that you have seen, all the cases you've been involved in, and so on, do you think there is a coherent argument to just have tougher gun laws in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I don't agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Why are you going all out then against President Obama over this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, it's actual fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, there's nothing wrong with flexibility.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Ben Labolt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Governor Romney in this letter would have undermined the work requirement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Labolt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "It's got a certain ring to it, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I think I'd have to agree with Governor Romney when he called that Obama-loney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "When a Great White Shark sinks its fangs into you, what does it feel like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, people ask me if I knew it was a shark.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Great White Shark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Why did you stay so cool?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I think the most surprising thing to me about this whole incident is that I didn't actually feel afraid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Was your son as phlegmatic about it all as you clearly were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "It's harder for me to know what was going through his mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "No, you wouldn't stick around to chat, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Or is it simply that with the modern media phenomena, that when there is an attack like this, it gets such a huge play on the Twitter-verse, if you like, that it seems like there are a lot more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "People's fear of shark attacks -- and I spoke to a couple of folks today, and they said God, I would never get in the water.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "And if that is true, why do they keep gnawing it at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "We speculate that that's the case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Chris, you say you were swimming back with your son.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "When you actually got back to land, what was your reaction then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Euphoria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Did you realize then the enormity of what you just survived?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "How is your leg?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I'm walking around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Is winning an Olympic gold for you the absolute number one dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "For all seven hours of the day, you're think of that gold medal, the podium, the American anthem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yeah, definitely, especially in the car ride to and from gym.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["seven hours of the day"]}}]